<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ArrayOfResource xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>0</ResourceId>
    <Name>Emeros Crystal</Name>
    <Description>Emeros Crystal is a brilliant green gemstone. It is typically used in weapons components. Emeros crystal is found on Volcanic worlds and occasionally at Carbonaceous worlds.</Description>
    <BaseCost>8</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/EmerosCrystal</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses />
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>1</ResourceId>
    <Name>Nekros Stone</Name>
    <Description>Nekros Stone is a deep red gemstone used in weapons components. Nekros stone is found on Volcanic worlds and occasionally at Rocky Desert worlds.</Description>
    <BaseCost>5</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/NekrosStone</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses />
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>2</ResourceId>
    <Name>Osalia</Name>
    <Description>Osalia is a purple gemstone used in weapons components. Osalia stones are found at Volcanic, Desert and Continental worlds.</Description>
    <BaseCost>11</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/Osalia</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses />
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>3</ResourceId>
    <Name>Kaasian Crystal</Name>
    <Description>Kaasian Crystal is a rare aqua-blue gemstone. It is typically used in high-end weapons components. Kaasian Crystal is found on Ocean worlds.</Description>
    <BaseCost>18</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/KaasianCrystal</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses />
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>4</ResourceId>
    <Name>Argon</Name>
    <Description>Argon is an inert yellow gas. It is typically used in weapons, shielding and reactor components. Argon is found at Gas Giant and Frozen Gas Giant worlds.</Description>
    <BaseCost>7</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/Argon</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses />
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>5</ResourceId>
    <Name>Krypton</Name>
    <Description>Krypton is an inert green gas. It is typically used in weapons, shielding and reactor components. Trace quantities are found at Gas Giant and Frozen Gas Giant worlds.</Description>
    <BaseCost>10</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/Krypton</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses />
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>6</ResourceId>
    <Name>Tyderios</Name>
    <Description>Tyderios is a rare inert gas used in weapons, shielding and reactor components. Tyderios gas has a pinkish tinge. It is heavier than air and will sink to ground-level unless buoyed by other surrounding gases. It is found in trace quantities at Ice and Frozen Gas Giant worlds.</Description>
    <BaseCost>15</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/Tyderios</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses />
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>7</ResourceId>
    <Name>Silicon</Name>
    <Description>Silicon is used in electronic components and energy collectors. It is found at Rocky Silicon and Desert worlds.</Description>
    <BaseCost>5</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/Silicon</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses />
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>8</ResourceId>
    <Name>Steel</Name>
    <Description>Steel is a very common construction material smelted from iron ore. Large amounts of steel are required to build most ships and bases. Iron ore is usually found at Rocky Metallic and Continental worlds, or asteroids.</Description>
    <BaseCost>5</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/Steel</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses />
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>9</ResourceId>
    <Name>Mebnar</Name>
    <Description>Mebnar is a very dense metal smelted from Mebnar ore. It has a dull dark grey, almost black appearance. It is particularly useful as heavy shielding in Reactor components. Mebnar is often found at Rocky Metallic worlds and asteroids</Description>
    <BaseCost>6</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/Mebnar</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses />
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>10</ResourceId>
    <Name>Aculon</Name>
    <Description>Aculon is a very strong, heat-resistant blue metal smelted from Aculon ore. It is typically used in components that are exposed to extreme temperatures. Aculon ore is found at Volcanic and Rocky Metallic worlds and at asteroids.</Description>
    <BaseCost>12</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/Aculon</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses />
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>11</ResourceId>
    <Name>Cuprica</Name>
    <Description>Cuprica is a shiny metal smelted from Cuprica ore. It is extremely strong and light-weight and has a shiny red-brown appearance. Cuprica is commonly used in beam and torpedo weapons. It is found at some Rocky Metallic planets and at asteroids.</Description>
    <BaseCost>18</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/Cuprica</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses />
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>12</ResourceId>
    <Name>Polymer</Name>
    <Description>Polymers are various types of plastics, usually produced from petroleum. It is typically used in electronic components. Polymer is found at Ocean, Marshy Swamp and Continental worlds.</Description>
    <BaseCost>6</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/Polymer</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses />
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>13</ResourceId>
    <Name>Carbonite</Name>
    <Description>Carbonite is a super-strong carbon compound. It is typically used in components that require great strength and resistance to high temperatures. Carbonite is found at Marshy Swamp, Mangrove Forest, Continental and Carbonaceous worlds.</Description>
    <BaseCost>9</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/Carbonite</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses />
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>14</ResourceId>
    <Name>Caslon</Name>
    <Description>Caslon is a common gas that is a universal reactor fuel. It is found at Gas Giant worlds.</Description>
    <BaseCost>3</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/Caslon</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses />
  </Resource>
  
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>15</ResourceId>
    <Name>Loros Fruit</Name>
    <Description>Loros Fruit is an extremely rare, sweet pink fruit of the Loros tree. It is prized for its amazing restorative properties, as well as its rich flavor and velvety texture. Loros fruit dramatically increases lifespan. The natural aging process is slowed radically, allowing a being to live much longer than normal. Any colony supplied with Loros fruit thus receives a large development bonus, over and above any other bonus. Once discovered, every effort should be made to control the trade of this highly valuable resource. Loros fruit grows only on Marshy Swamp worlds.</Description>
    <BaseCost>200</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/LorosFruit</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.26</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyPopulationGrowthRate</Type>
        <Amount>0.04</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>PlagueCuring</Type>
        <Amount>0.15</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Empire</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>16</ResourceId>
    <Name>Megallos Nut</Name>
    <Description>Megallos Nut is the tangy yellow nut of the Megallos tree. These trees have a gnarled, twisted appearance. They grow very slowly, usually taking 2,000 years to reach a mature height of 5 meters. Their vast root system can spread for up to 30 meters in every direction. They grow deep within dense forests on Continental worlds.</Description>
    <BaseCost>12</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/MegallosNut</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.03</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyPopulationGrowthRate</Type>
        <Amount>0.01</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>17</ResourceId>
    <Name>Falajian Spice</Name>
    <Description>Falajian Spice is a powdery brown spice harvested from the Falajian bush. It is highly valued for its distinctive rich flavor. Falajian spice is used extensively in exotic cuisine. Falajian spice is made from the leaves of the Falajian bush by slowly drying them and then grinding them to a fine powder. Falajian bushes grow in swampy ponds on Marshy Swamp worlds.</Description>
    <BaseCost>20</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/FalajianSpice</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.04</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>18</ResourceId>
    <Name>Korabbian Spice</Name>
    <Description>Korabbian Spice is an extremely rare crystallized white spice. It is valued for its unique medicinal properties. Under special circumstances deposits of Korabbian spice will spontaneously accumulate on the walls of rocky canyons. The exact process that forms Korabbian spice has never been precisely identified. But it is theorized that the spice is created by a chemical reaction between certain types of rocks and the harsh, hot winds that sometimes gust through the canyons. It dramatically increases mental sharpness, allowing a being to perform incredible intellectual feats. Any colony supplied with Korabbian spice thus receives a large development bonus, over and above any other bonus. Once discovered, every effort should be made to control the trade of this highly valuable resource. Korabbian spice is found exclusively on Desert worlds.</Description>
    <BaseCost>180</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/KorabbianSpice</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.22</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyHappiness</Type>
        <Amount>0.15</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ResearchAll</Type>
        <Amount>0.05</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Empire</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>19</ResourceId>
    <Name>Ekarus Meat</Name>
    <Description>Ekarus Meat is the tender meat of the Ekarus beast. The Ekarus is a fierce predator that inhabits watery bogs on Marshy Swamp worlds. It can remain submerged underwater for hours at a time, only surfacing when it locates suitable prey swimming above.</Description>
    <BaseCost>18</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/EkarusMeat</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.03</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyPopulationGrowthRate</Type>
        <Amount>0.01</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>20</ResourceId>
    <Name>Nepthys Wine</Name>
    <Description>Nepthys Wine is a fine wine made from Nepthys seaweed. Enormous forests of the seaweed grow deep beneath the oceans. Stands of the seaweed can reach heights of 40 meters or more. Nepthys seaweed is unique to Ocean worlds.</Description>
    <BaseCost>22</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/NepthysWine</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.04</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyHappiness</Type>
        <Amount>0.02</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>21</ResourceId>
    <Name>Rephidium Ale</Name>
    <Description>Rephidium Ale is a delicious, super-dry beer. Several different variations of Rephidium ale are produced. Some of these blends use secret ingredients. However the primary common ingredient is the leaves and stalks of the Repha bush. Rephidium Ale is produced on Forest worlds.</Description>
    <BaseCost>8</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/RephidiumAle</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.02</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyHappiness</Type>
        <Amount>0.01</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>22</ResourceId>
    <Name>Wiconium</Name>
    <Description>Wiconium is an incredibly sweet type of alcohol made from the rare Wiconius plant. This plant is a cactus-like succulent. It has thick spongy leaves that contain the rich Wiconium juice. The Wiconius plant is found only on Desert Savanna worlds.</Description>
    <BaseCost>19</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/Wiconium</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.04</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyHappiness</Type>
        <Amount>0.02</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>23</ResourceId>
    <Name>Vodkol</Name>
    <Description>Vodkol is a powerful alcoholic beverage made from the roots of the Vodia plant. This hardy plant grows in the tundra wastelands of Ice worlds. Above ground the Vodia plant appears as a scraggly shrub with broad, pale yellow leaves. Below ground it has bulbous, white roots.</Description>
    <BaseCost>13</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/Vodkol</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.03</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyHappiness</Type>
        <Amount>0.01</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>24</ResourceId>
    <Name>Questurian Skin</Name>
    <Description>Questurian Skin is the soft, scaly skin of the Questurian, an enormous aquatic reptile. Questurians are deadly predators that can grow to lengths of 100 meters or more. They inhabit dark undersea tunnels and caves in the depths of vast oceans. They are found exclusively on Ocean worlds.</Description>
    <BaseCost>27</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/QuesturianSkin</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.06</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>25</ResourceId>
    <Name>Bifurian Silk</Name>
    <Description>Bifurian Silk is an extremely fine shimmering blue silk, spun by the Bifuria worm. Bifuria worms live deep in dark underground caves on Grasslands and Continental worlds. They attach themselves to the ceiling and walls of damp grottos and spin vast webs of ultra-fine gossamer fibers. These fibers can be collected and woven into Bifurian silk.</Description>
    <BaseCost>33</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/BifurianSilk</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.07</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyIncome</Type>
        <Amount>0.01</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>26</ResourceId>
    <Name>Caguar Fur</Name>
    <Description>Caguar Fur is the luxuriant fur of the striped Caguar. The Caguar is a huge sabre-cat that prowls the wild rainforests of Forest and Marshy Swamp worlds. The adult length of a Caguar from nose to tail is approximately 4 meters. They have razor-sharp claws that they use to capture their prey.</Description>
    <BaseCost>31</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/CaguarFur</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.08</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>27</ResourceId>
    <Name>Terallion Down</Name>
    <Description>Terallion Down is the soft white down of the Terallion beast. Terallions are four-legged birds that inhabit the tundra wastelands of Frozen Ice worlds. They have a vast wingspan that can reach 6 meters. Terallions hunt small rodents, or even sentient species like Jintus or Ugnari.</Description>
    <BaseCost>19</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/TerallionDown</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.05</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyIncome</Type>
        <Amount>0.01</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>28</ResourceId>
    <Name>Dantha Fur</Name>
    <Description>Dantha Fur is the shaggy brown-white fur of the Dantha. Danthas are large animals that live on the vast desert plains of Desert worlds. They live in herds ranging in size from 30 to 200. Danthas migrate across the desert in search of food. Their preferred diet are the Lopid fungii that grow about half a meter beneath the desert sands. Danthas have a highly-developed sense of smell that allows them to locate these water-bearing fungal growths and dig them out.</Description>
    <BaseCost>14</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/DanthaFur</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.04</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>29</ResourceId>
    <Name>Aquasian Incense</Name>
    <Description>Aquasian Incense is an intense blue-colored perfume. It is made from a combination of various unique ingredients found on Ocean worlds. The primary ingredient is poisonous spines from Dakhul deep sea anemones. Another constituent is brilliant blue Orkton coral, crushed to a fine powder.</Description>
    <BaseCost>29</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/AquasianIncense</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.06</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyPopulationGrowthRate</Type>
        <Amount>0.01</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>30</ResourceId>
    <Name>Natarran Incense</Name>
    <Description>Natarran Incense is a beautiful but subtle perfume made from the Natarril plant. Natarril is a small shrub with tiny blue-green leaves and dazzling multi-color flowers. It is typically found clinging to rocky cliff-faces on Rocky Desert worlds.</Description>
    <BaseCost>26</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/NatarranIncense</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.07</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyHappiness</Type>
        <Amount>0.01</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>31</ResourceId>
    <Name>Zentabia Fluid</Name>
    <Description>Zentabia Fluid is a potent healing fluid made from the rare Zentabia flower. These flowers occasionally grow in sheltered crevices on Volcanic worlds. Their petals are colored a brilliant green. They thrive in very hot environments. Zentabia fluid can heal nearly any wound or disease. It can even repair damaged limbs or organs. Any colony supplied with Zentabia fluid thus receives a large development bonus, over and above any other bonus. Once discovered, every effort should be made to control the trade of this highly valuable resource.</Description>
    <BaseCost>190</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/ZentabiaFluid</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.24</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyHappiness</Type>
        <Amount>0.1</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>TroopRecoveryRate</Type>
        <Amount>0.5</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>PlagueCuring</Type>
        <Amount>0.03</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>32</ResourceId>
    <Name>Ilosian Jade</Name>
    <Description>Ilosian Jade is a beautiful translucent green stone. It is mined in great slabs from riverbed rocks. Ilosian jade is found exclusively on Marshy Swamp worlds.</Description>
    <BaseCost>20</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/IlosianJade</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.06</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>33</ResourceId>
    <Name>Otandium Opal</Name>
    <Description>Otandium Opal is a brilliant, sparkling, multi-colored stone. Otandium opals are found on the shores of lava lakes on Volcanic worlds. They are produced when certain types of lava cools very quickly.</Description>
    <BaseCost>20</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/OtandiumOpal</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.05</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyIncome</Type>
        <Amount>0.01</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>34</ResourceId>
    <Name>Jakanta Ivory</Name>
    <Description>Jakanta Ivory comes from the ivory tusks of the Jakanta ice-beast. Jakantas are reclusive creatures that inhabit the mountains of Ice planets. They are large, six-legged bear-like animals with thick shaggy white fur. Their tusks can grow to lengths exceeding 3 meters.</Description>
    <BaseCost>23</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/JakantaIvory</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.07</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>35</ResourceId>
    <Name>Ucantium Pearl</Name>
    <Description>Ucantium Pearls are enormous pink and blue pearls that grow in the Ucantium clam, a shell-fish found deep in the seas of Ocean worlds. The Ucantium clam can live for thousands of years and can reach diameters of 5 meters or more. A single clam can produce hundreds of pearls.</Description>
    <BaseCost>31</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/UcantiumPearl</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.08</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyIncome</Type>
        <Amount>0.01</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>36</ResourceId>
    <Name>Yarras Marble</Name>
    <Description>Yarras Marble is a magnificently textured blue marble. Yarras marble is formed when carbonate rocks are infused with millions of tiny blue Agea crystals. This is usually caused by underground streams flowing through the rocky formations for thousands of years. Yarras marble is found on Continental worlds.</Description>
    <BaseCost>20</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/YarrasMarble</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.05</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>

  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>37</ResourceId>
    <Name>Podanthia Root</Name>
    <Description>Podanthia Root is a medicinal herb that helps cure many diseases. It’s fine, fibrous stems are packed with powerful nutrients that reinforce the immune system. It is found at Sulphur Volcanic worlds.</Description>
    <BaseCost>30</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/PodanthiaRoot</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.06</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyPopulationGrowthRate</Type>
        <Amount>0.02</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>38</ResourceId>
    <Name>Vofula Scent</Name>
    <Description>Vofula Scent is an intoxicating perfume that comes from the brilliant green flowers of the Vofula plant. The Vofula plant is a small bush that grows next to the hydrocarbon lakes on Carbonaceous worlds.</Description>
    <BaseCost>20</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/VofulaScent</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.04</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>39</ResourceId>
    <Name>Suculos Wood</Name>
    <Description>Suculos is a rare exotic timber from the Suculos tree. The very hard wood of this tree has a deep red color with a beautiful grain and texture. Suculos trees grow to enormous heights of 400 meters or more. They are found on the vast bushlands of Desert Savanna worlds.</Description>
    <BaseCost>20</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/SucculosWood</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.04</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>40</ResourceId>
    <Name>Copandil</Name>
    <Description>Copandil is a very strong liquor that is fermented from the bulbs of the Copandil bush. The concentrated yellow fluid has an intense fiery flavour. It is found on Grasslands worlds.</Description>
    <BaseCost>25</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/Copandil</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.04</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyHappiness</Type>
        <Amount>0.01</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>41</ResourceId>
    <Name>Norjak Eggs</Name>
    <Description>These eggs are laid by the Norjak - an enormous otter-like creature found on Ice planets. Norjak eggs are typically 30-40 cm in size and have a light blue color. They are valued for their delicate flavour and are highly nutritious.</Description>
    <BaseCost>20</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/NorjakEggs</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.03</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyPopulationGrowthRate</Type>
        <Amount>0.01</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>42</ResourceId>
    <Name>Breqiian Berries</Name>
    <Description>Breqiian berries are the tiny purple fruit of the Breqiian vine. These vines grow high in the tree canopy of the vast jungles of Forest worlds. The Breqiian vine draws nutrients from its host tree, thus giving each vine and its berries a slightly different flavour.</Description>
    <BaseCost>20</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/BreqiianBerries</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.05</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>43</ResourceId>
    <Name>Kasotti</Name>
    <Description>Kasotti is a creamy alcoholic drink that comes from the thick, juicy leaves of the Kasot plant, a ground-covering herb that grows in the lowland coastal plains of Ice Tundra worlds.</Description>
    <BaseCost>15</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/Kasotti</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.03</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>44</ResourceId>
    <Name>Oksunum Steak</Name>
    <Description>Oksunum are sure-footed goat-like creatures that inhabit the secluded canyons of Rocky Desert worlds. They feed on many delicate mosses and lichens that grow in the shady side ravines. This gives their tender meat a delicious flavour.</Description>
    <BaseCost>20</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/OksunumSteak</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.05</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyPopulationGrowthRate</Type>
        <Amount>0.01</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>45</ResourceId>
    <Name>Attarion Fur</Name>
    <Description>Attarions are predatory cats that live high in the mountains of Frozen Ice worlds. They grow to 2 meters in length, and have beautiful grey-white fur. The fur is extremely soft and light. It is prized for its warmth and durability when used in clothing.</Description>
    <BaseCost>25</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/AttarionFur</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.04</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyHappiness</Type>
        <Amount>0.01</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>46</ResourceId>
    <Name>Muurion Wine</Name>
    <Description>Muurion plants are tall bamboo-like shoots that can reach 15 meters in height. They grow on the vast plains of Grassland worlds. Muurion plants have many small fragrant flowers. The yellow petals of these flowers are used to make Muurion wine.</Description>
    <BaseCost>20</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/MuurionWine</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.04</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyHappiness</Type>
        <Amount>0.01</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>47</ResourceId>
    <Name>Inkasdia Fruit</Name>
    <Description>Inkasdia Fruit grows on small bushes in the swamps of Mangrove Forest worlds. The fruit has a tough purple exterior with fuzzy spikes. But inside is a soft, rich, juicy flesh prized for its delightful flavour and texture.</Description>
    <BaseCost>20</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/InkasdiaFruit</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.04</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>48</ResourceId>
    <Name>Feraxian Firestone</Name>
    <Description>Feraxian Firestones are sometimes found on Sulphur Volcanic worlds. They form when part of the planetary core is forced upwards by active sulphur volcanoes. The cooling core often contains firestones, named not only for their origin but because they seemingly glow from within when caught by rays of light. They are usually a brilliant yellow-gold color, but there is also a rare but naturally occurring luminous blue firestone.</Description>
    <BaseCost>35</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/FeraxianFirestone</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.08</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyIncome</Type>
        <Amount>0.01</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>49</ResourceId>
    <Name>Vakala Crystal</Name>
    <Description>Vakala Crystals can produce a dazzling display of colors when light shines through them. They have the unique ability to also convert non-visible light into the visible spectrum, thus allowing visibility of infra-red and ultra-violet rays. Vakala Crystals are found near the shoreline of hydrocarbon lakes on Carbonaceous worlds.</Description>
    <BaseCost>32</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/VakalaCrystal</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.07</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyIncome</Type>
        <Amount>0.01</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>50</ResourceId>
    <Name>Decarion Ale</Name>
    <Description>Decarion Ale is a strong, bright-red colored alcohol that is made on Ice Tundra worlds. This alcohol comes from a small shrub called Decaria, which has yellow-red leaves. The alcohol is made from the roots of the plant, which reach deep into the ground. It is harvested in summer before being replanted in autumn.</Description>
    <BaseCost>24</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/DecarionAle</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.05</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyHappiness</Type>
        <Amount>0.01</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>51</ResourceId>
    <Name>Obrudan Amber</Name>
    <Description>Obrudan Amber is the iridescent red-orange resin from the Obrudan tree. These trees grow in small clumps on Marshy Swamp worlds. The bark of the tree is very fragile and when damaged the resin slowly leaks out and hardens on the trunk, creating the amber. It is often used in jewellery because of its eye-catching appearance.</Description>
    <BaseCost>20</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/ObrudanAmber</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.04</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>52</ResourceId>
    <Name>Yapara Leaf</Name>
    <Description>Yapara Leaf is a low-lying shrub that grows deep in the arid wastelands of Desert Savanna worlds. The leaves are a yellowish-green color. Yapara Leaf can withstand intense heat and can survive without water for almost 10 years. The leaves of this plant are packed full of powerful phytonutrients that are very effective at protecting against toxins and pathogens.</Description>
    <BaseCost>30</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/YaparaLeaf</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.03</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyPopulationGrowthRate</Type>
        <Amount>0.02</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>PlagueCuring</Type>
        <Amount>0.02</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>53</ResourceId>
    <Name>Giraxian Nectar</Name>
    <Description>Giraxian nectar is a potent medicine that is found on Continental worlds. The nectar is produced in large tubes of the flowers of the Giraxian tree. The nectar has a radiant pink color. It is refined and combined with other ingredients to create a medicine that helps to break fevers.</Description>
    <BaseCost>25</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/GiraxianNectar</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.02</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyPopulationGrowthRate</Type>
        <Amount>0.01</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>PlagueCuring</Type>
        <Amount>0.02</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>54</ResourceId>
    <Name>Hapek Obsidian</Name>
    <Description>This rare type of obsidian is found on the surface of some Forest worlds. It is a dazzling blue or teal colour. Hapek Obsidian is especially valued when crafted into knives, as obsidian blade can have a cutting edge many times sharper than metal knives. It’s beautiful colour means it is also prized as a gemstone in jewellery as well as made into tools and ornaments.</Description>
    <BaseCost>20</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/HapekObsidian</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.05</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyIncome</Type>
        <Amount>0.01</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>55</ResourceId>
    <Name>Lukaarin Fungus</Name>
    <Description>Lukaarin Fungus is a rare delicacy that grows in the shallow waters around the roots of mangrove trees. Hundreds of these small brown nodules grow together in large masses. They are very sweet and have an intense aroma. They are found exclusively on Mangrove Forest worlds.</Description>
    <BaseCost>25</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/LukaarianFungus</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.06</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>56</ResourceId>
    <Name>Rhylig</Name>
    <Description>Rhylig is a crystal that naturally projects 3D holograms when light falls on it. Rhylig is created by pure molten lava interacting with obsidian rock. It has a dark orange color and is typically found on the shores of molten lava rivers on Volcanic worlds.</Description>
    <BaseCost>20</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/RhyligCrystal</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.05</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>57</ResourceId>
    <Name>Shudasta Scales</Name>
    <Description>Shudasta Scales are the super-tough scaly skins of the giant Shudasta lizards. These lizards live mostly solitary lives on Rocky Desert worlds and can grow very large, some of the largest being 11 or 12 metres in length. They can be hard to capture and kill, but their skin is very valuable, used in clothing and chair coverings. The scales are a silvery grey color.</Description>
    <BaseCost>30</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/ShudastaScales</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.04</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDefense</Type>
        <Amount>0.01</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>TroopGroundDefense</Type>
        <Amount>0.02</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>58</ResourceId>
    <Name>Tebraakian Granite</Name>
    <Description>Tebraakian Granite is found only on Volcanic worlds. It is formed by magma mixing with basalt and being forced deeper underground. As the magma cools it forms crystals that have a radiant red glow. Tebraakian Granite comes in a mixture of colours such as red, white, grey and black. It is a very hard granite that is used to decorate and construct buildings.</Description>
    <BaseCost>20</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/TebraakianGranite</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.05</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyIncome</Type>
        <Amount>0.01</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>59</ResourceId>
    <Name>Xukantar</Name>
    <Description>Xukantar is a potent perfume distilled partly from an exotic type of Deep Ocean seaweed. The seaweed is purple in colour and has flat, crinkly leaves. When squeezed the leaves excrete a deep purple liquid with a beautiful scent. The liquid is occasionally used to dye fabrics, but more commonly it is used as a perfume. The reason for the rarity of this perfume is the very small amount of liquid produced from large amounts of seaweed, and thus it is always in demand.</Description>
    <BaseCost>35</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/Xukantar</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.09</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>

  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>60</ResourceId>
    <Name>Korduva Grain</Name>
    <Description>Korduva Grain is grown on Grassland worlds. This grain grows on very tall stalks of 3-4 meters in height. Each stalk can have millions of grain heads, thus producing colossal harvests. The grain is a beige color and is valued for its high nutrition and pleasant flavour.</Description>
    <BaseCost>25</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/KorduvaGrain</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.03</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyPopulationGrowthRate</Type>
        <Amount>0.02</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>61</ResourceId>
    <Name>Losarn Syrup</Name>
    <Description>Losarn Syrup is the thick sweet sap of the Losarn tree. Large forests of Losarn trees are farmed on Continental worlds. Losarn Syrup has a rich golden color and it is universally appreciated for its delicious flavour.</Description>
    <BaseCost>18</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/LosarnSyrup</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.04</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>62</ResourceId>
    <Name>Akrasan Amber</Name>
    <Description>Akrasan Amber is the sap of the Akrasan tree, which grows in areas of dense mist on Mangrove Forest planets. Akrasan trees have large hollow cavities. These cavities inside the tree act as insulated ovens, where the sap gets boiling hot. Weak sections of the tree trunk often explode from the pressure of the hot sap. The sap oozes out and bugs are attracted to it. They become stuck in the sap. The cool mist sets the sap hard, forming the beautiful golden amber.</Description>
    <BaseCost>20</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/AkrasanAmber</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.04</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>63</ResourceId>
    <Name>Doakan Tea</Name>
    <Description>Doakan Tea is made from the leaves of Doakan bamboo. It grows in shady areas in the mountainous regions of Desert Savanna planets. It does not require much water to survive, making the leaves crinkly and scratchy. Tea made from the leaves has lots of flavour.</Description>
    <BaseCost>20</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/DoakanTea</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.04</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>64</ResourceId>
    <Name>Yotapian Onyx</Name>
    <Description>Yotapian Onyx is a deep purple-black gemstone that is found in shallow underground caves on Rocky Desert planets. It is highly esteemed for its interaction with other gemstones, intensifying and deepening their colors. For this reason it is often used in jewellery.</Description>
    <BaseCost>20</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/YotapianOnyx</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.05</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>65</ResourceId>
    <Name>Hyutil Resin</Name>
    <Description>Hyutil Resin comes from bulbous plants on the deep ocean floor. These plants secrete the resin, especially when exposed to ultraviolet light. Hyutil Resin is most often a dark translucent red or purple, but blue and brown Hyutil Resin have also been found. The resin is extremely strong and must be exposed to high temperatures to be shaped into delicate utensils and ornaments, in which form it is most highly prized. It is found exclusively on Deep Ocean worlds.</Description>
    <BaseCost>21</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/HyutilResin</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.06</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>66</ResourceId>
    <Name>Darkhul Tentacles</Name>
    <Description>Darkhuls are formidable sea monsters that inhabit the bottomless undersea tunnels of Deep Ocean worlds. Darkhuls can grow to lengths of 100 meters or more. They are apex predators that fear nothing. Hunting these terrifying creatures is thus a perilous task, fraught with danger. Darkhul tentacles are a rare delicacy used as food and medicine across the galaxy.</Description>
    <BaseCost>45</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/DarkhulTentacles</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.08</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyPopulationGrowthRate</Type>
        <Amount>0.03</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>67</ResourceId>
    <Name>Sokalian Brandy</Name>
    <Description>Sokalian Brandy is distilled from Sokalian plum wine. The wine is made from rare Sokalian plums, which are a deep pink in colour. Sokalian plum trees grow only in the highland regions of Sandy Desert worlds. Sokalian Brandy is widely renowned for its caramel flavor and beautiful pink color. It is usually aged for more than 50 years to enrich its flavour.</Description>
    <BaseCost>30</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/SokalianBrandy</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.06</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyHappiness</Type>
        <Amount>0.01</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>68</ResourceId>
    <Name>Bartak Wood</Name>
    <Description>Bartak Wood is the very dense timber of the Bartak tree, found mainly on Forest worlds. It has a beautiful dark brown grain and a very fine, smooth finish when sawn. It can be carved into furniture or used for building. Bartak trees can reach mammoth sizes, taking many centuries to reach heights of up to 300 meters.</Description>
    <BaseCost>20</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/BartakWood</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.05</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyIncome</Type>
        <Amount>0.01</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>69</ResourceId>
    <Name>Wruzos Anemone</Name>
    <Description>Wruzos Anemone floats in small clusters on the ocean’s surface, and is harvested for food. An interesting characteristic of this rare anemone is that it relaxes and expands in sunlight but contracts when exposed to stormy weather. It is considered a great delicacy, and usually marinated in various sauces or spices before being eaten. It is usually cream or pale pink in colour. Wruzos Anemones are found exclusively on Ocean worlds.</Description>
    <BaseCost>20</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/WruzosAnemone</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.05</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>70</ResourceId>
    <Name>Tassont Moth Fiber</Name>
    <Description>The gigantic Tassont Moths are the largest of their species. They live deep in vast caves on Sandy Desert worlds, where the climate is most comfortable for them. The ingenious fiber of their wings can bear enormous loads though it is only a few microns thick. It is much in demand for use in garment making and tailoring ceremonial costumes. But it is also used in structural and safety work, such as rock climbing.</Description>
    <BaseCost>27</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/TassontMothFibre</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.06</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyIncome</Type>
        <Amount>0.01</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>71</ResourceId>
    <Name>Ordulos Shell</Name>
    <Description>The rare Ordulos Shell is found on some Ocean worlds. The shells are small and roughly oval in shape, and very uniform in size. The outside is coated in an iridescent substance that provides a shimmering display of colours, much like an imperfect natural prism. The shells were once widely used as a form of currency on some worlds but are now primarily used as ornaments and in decorating clothes.</Description>
    <BaseCost>24</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/OrdulosShell</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.06</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyIncome</Type>
        <Amount>0.01</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>72</ResourceId>
    <Name>Tebrullian Moss</Name>
    <Description>Tebrullian Moss grows on a rare species of tree that grows horizontally off the ice cliffs of some Ice worlds. The moss is a pale grey color, and grows in strands draping from the tree trunks. It is used in many cuisines as a herb or garnish for certain dishes, and is considered a rare delicacy.</Description>
    <BaseCost>20</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/TebrullianMoss</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.05</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>73</ResourceId>
    <Name>Sarrobia Coral</Name>
    <Description>Sarrobia Coral is very hard and sharp. It grows underwater in shallow coastal areas on Ocean planets. It comes in various colors such as turquoise, jade, and violet. The sunlight from some star types can make the coral sparkly and beautiful.</Description>
    <BaseCost>17</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/SarrobiaCoral</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.04</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>74</ResourceId>
    <Name>Korhuga Beans</Name>
    <Description>Korhuga Beans grow on a small thorny tree found on Sandy Desert worlds. The tree takes many decades to grow to maturity. Once it finally matures it produces small bean pods that are collected and dried. Korhuga Beans are a tasty but very spicy foodstuff used as an ingredient in the dishes of many desert cultures. It is also used by many chefs throughout the galaxy.</Description>
    <BaseCost>16</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/KorhugaBeans</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.04</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>75</ResourceId>
    <Name>Ardilus Tentacles</Name>
    <Description>Ardiluses are large, deep-space monsters that typically lurk near Gas Giant planets. Hunting them yields the prized Ardilus tentacles. These tentacles have many uses: some parts can be eaten, other parts produce dye. The spiny protrusions are popular in decorative construction.</Description>
    <BaseCost>60</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/ArdilusTentacles</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.15</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>76</ResourceId>
    <Name>Gravillex Crystal</Name>
    <Description>Gravillex are crystalline space monsters that typically live near the coronas of exotic star types. Hunting these Gravillex yields their unique crystal structures. The crystals can have a range of dazzling colors. They have special holographic properties that make them highly sought after as jewelry and decorations.</Description>
    <BaseCost>45</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/GravillexCrystal</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses>
      <Bonus>
        <Type>ColonyDevelopment</Type>
        <Amount>0.11</Amount>
        <AppliesTo>Item</AppliesTo>
      </Bonus>
    </Bonuses>
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>77</ResourceId>
    <Name>Dyrillium Quartz</Name>
    <Description>Dyrillium Quartz is used in high-end electronic components and energy collectors. It is found at Sulphur Volcanic worlds.</Description>
    <BaseCost>12</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/DyrilliumQuartz</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses />
  </Resource>
  <Resource>
    <ResourceId>78</ResourceId>
    <Name>Hexodorium</Name>
    <Description>Hexodorium is a unique type of polymer. It is very strong and damage resistant. It has many uses in various high-end components. Hexodorium is usually found at Frozen Ice worlds, although other Ice planets may also have small deposits.</Description>
    <BaseCost>19</BaseCost>
    <ImageFilename>Environment/Resources/Hexodorium</ImageFilename>
    <Bonuses />
  </Resource>
</ArrayOfResource>